Sometimes it takes man's best friend to show what
it really means to be a family.
The Retrievers is a comedy, family, tv movie film directed by Paul Schneider.
The Lowrys are starting a new life, moving to the quiet
Northern California town of Placerville.
But when they are "adopted" by a clever yet lovable stray Golden
Retriever, their lives change in ways they never imagined.
It's not long before the Lowrys discover that Pilot is pregnant.
But when it comes time to find new homes for the puppies, the Lowrys learn how hard it can be to say goodbye
and how a determined Golden Retriever can show them a thing or two about the bonds of family.
Pilot wants her puppies back!
Can the Lowrys retrieve the Retrievers from the wacky
cast of characters that adopted them?
The Retrievers is a heartwarming story about how a stray Golden Retriever, along with her litter of pups,
teaches the Lowrys some big lessons about life, love, family, and what's truly important.
Tom Lowry, played by Robert Hays.
Karen Lowry, played by Mel Harris.
Ed, played by Alan Rachins.
Liz Lowry, played by Alana Austin.
Widdy Lowry, played by Taylor Emerson.
Mrs. Krisper, played by Betty White.
The Retrievers is a 2001 television film starring Robert Hays, Mel Harris, Alan
Rachins, Alana Austin, Taylor Emerson, Betty White and Robert Wagner.
It was directed by Paul Schneider and written by Larry Ketron.
The tone is lighthearted and uplifting and emotional.